{
    "id": "69c2b1b5c26c4578b9bca64b487dfc17",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have lived here ........................................ 10 years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a66a0d6c94042c29d831c9ba639a596"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ............................................. stealing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70592ccd88cf46698f5ee45b7e7ae254"
        },
        {
            "question": "We .......................................... the work yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5d271d315cf4d67af4703abe36c86b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t get well unless you ......................................... your medicine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "are taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e008ebbf3bb9454d97f365f52c30a662"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been living in this house ...................................... five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea9568155a08408f97bca9091ff3a381"
        },
        {
            "question": "We .............................................. English for the last seven years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are learning",
                "learns",
                "have been learning"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "13c13516960d48588a331bca9d2d3879"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday ........................................... a holiday, he went to see a film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "being"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f448721d44d47338a6d58a90fef8120"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new headmaster wants a house to ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "live in",
                "live at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81c6314cb9b9410d87e63e4948d66678"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................................ for you since 9 o’clock in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am waiting",
                "waited",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "62b804c3785c43cea64918855dafd8c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ all the books to the library yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "have returned",
                "has returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd545098531845b4b82c59caa13edc0e"
        }
    ]
}